[{"answer": "Well, maybe.", "docId": "131220pmt", "aSentId": 28, "question": "Is that -- does that happen?", "qSentId": 27}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "131220pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "ECK: What's faith play a role in your life?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "Carol Roth, what's the name, Newt Gingrich, Mitch McConnell, you know, everybody that can make my life a living hell as I have a network.", "docId": "131220pmt", "aSentId": 52, "question": "What's wrong with them?", "qSentId": 51}, {"answer": "I think that, you know, you have people that are old in firm that -- and don't have a church, don't have a family, don't have anybody to go to, but that I think is for the local community.", "docId": "131220pmt", "aSentId": 56, "question": "Give me, for instance, what's an example of one of those?", "qSentId": 55}, {"answer": "No ...", "docId": "131220pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "Is he wrong?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "No, I don't.", "docId": "131220pmt", "aSentId": 68, "question": "You seem to delight in identifying heretics?", "qSentId": 67}, {"answer": "It should help all mankind.", "docId": "131220pmt", "aSentId": 113, "question": "I mean, who's going to harness that?", "qSentId": 112}, {"answer": "Don't care.", "docId": "131220pmt", "aSentId": 137, "question": "We don't want to win?", "qSentId": 136}, {"answer": "Conservatives don't want to win and it's ...", "docId": "131220pmt", "aSentId": 140, "question": "Win for what?", "qSentId": 139}, {"answer": "He is a progressive.", "docId": "131220pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "How so, how so?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "Yeah, OK.", "docId": "131220pmt", "aSentId": 149, "question": "Have you looked into that?", "qSentId": 148}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "131220pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "... where he stands on that?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "I'm not.", "docId": "131220pmt", "aSentId": 164, "question": "Are you comfortable with that?", "qSentId": 163}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "131220pmt", "aSentId": 170, "question": "The key here is, are you for maximum freedom?", "qSentId": 169}, {"answer": "I don't know because I don't trust any of them.", "docId": "131220pmt", "aSentId": 181, "question": "So, who do -- who would you like for 2016 if you could anoint someone today?", "qSentId": 180}, {"answer": "I like Ted Cruz a lot.", "docId": "131220pmt", "aSentId": 184, "question": "You like Ted Cruz a lot?", "qSentId": 183}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "131220pmt", "aSentId": 187, "question": "But can he win or you don't care?", "qSentId": 186}, {"answer": "Let's see.", "docId": "131220pmt", "aSentId": 191, "question": "Who does that if we don't get conservatives elected?", "qSentId": 190}, {"answer": "... only second to Nixon.", "docId": "131220pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "... assessment of the second term?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "131220pmt", "aSentId": 254, "question": "What's his second term looking like for you?", "qSentId": 253}, {"answer": "Yeah, I think, no.", "docId": "131220pmt", "aSentId": 343, "question": "Because you admit that's a problem, income inequality is real, it's wide and under Obama or no?", "qSentId": 342}, {"answer": "You're not going to solve it through government.", "docId": "131220pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "What's one thing conservative should be talking about?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "UPP: That's another question, I've seen it.", "docId": "131220pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "How much did we spend?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "Those are ...", "docId": "131220pmt", "aSentId": 392, "question": "What's your secret?", "qSentId": 391}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "131220pmt", "aSentId": 394, "question": "What are doing right?", "qSentId": 393}, {"answer": "The end game is to be is ubiquity (ph) as possible ...", "docId": "131220pmt", "aSentId": 415, "question": "... with TheBlaze TV, so what's the end game?", "qSentId": 414}, {"answer": "Yes, you.", "docId": "131220pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "Me?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "Not once.", "docId": "131220pmt", "aSentId": 431, "question": "Never?", "qSentId": 430}, {"answer": "I've already talked to God about it.", "docId": "131220pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "You won't tell us?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "I think so but I think also, you know, everybody is different, everybody has their own line.", "docId": "131220pmt", "aSentId": 454, "question": "So you think that we as folks with a platform or some level of influence on, have to be more responsible about the kinds of things you've talk about and the way we talk about them?", "qSentId": 453}, {"answer": "It's an attempt to a serious question.", "docId": "131220pmt", "aSentId": 465, "question": "Is that a serious question?", "qSentId": 464}, {"answer": "OK stay with me Glenn.", "docId": "131220pmt", "aSentId": 477, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 476}, {"answer": "Because I think that history is -- history has been made in the facts with dates and memorization of names and places where we've lost the story.", "docId": "131220pmt", "aSentId": 492, "question": "Why are you so fascinated with this old tiny artifact?", "qSentId": 491}, {"answer": "Just Google Topsy the Elephant.", "docId": "131220pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "How so?", "qSentId": 509}, {"answer": "Redemption, not survival, redemption.", "docId": "131220pmt", "aSentId": 557, "question": "How do you describe your life?", "qSentId": 556}, {"answer": "No, I find ...", "docId": "131220pmt", "aSentId": 573, "question": "Have you encouraged other people into that faith or faith in general?", "qSentId": 572}, {"answer": "No, I find that living a good example and showing people who are miserable, there's an easy -- there's an easier way.", "docId": "131220pmt", "aSentId": 575, "question": "Do you find that to be a mission of yours?", "qSentId": 574}]